Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LVI is arranged in 3 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LVII is arranged in 16 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LVI. BROTHERHOOD BONDING DEPARTMENT
  - Sub-Series 331-0. Brotherhood Bonding Department
    - General, 1930 (Box 508, Folder 118)
    - General, 1924 (Box 508, Folder 119)
    - General, 1932 (Box 508, Folder 120)
    - General, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 121)
  - Sub-Series 331-1. Brotherhood Bonding Department
    - Applications, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 122)
  - Sub-Series 331-2. Brotherhood Bonding Department
    - Lodges, 1931 (Box 508, Folder 123)
- Series LVII. UNITED STATES DEPARTMENT OF LABOR
  - Sub-Series 337-0. United States Department of Labor
    - General, 1948-1963 (Box 509, Folder 1)
      1948-December 1963.
    - General, 1963 (Box 509, Folder 2)
      February 21, 1963-July 1963.
    - Fiftieth Anniversary, 1962-1963 (Box 509, Folder 3)
    - General, 1962-1963 (Box 509, Folder 4)
      September 1962-February 20, 1963.
    - General, 1962 (Box 509, Folder 5)
      June-August 1962.
    - General, 1961 (Box 509, Folder 6)
      June 16, 1961-November 1961.
    - General, 1961 (Box 509, Folder 7)
      January 1961-July 15, 1961.
    - General, 1960 (Box 509, Folder 8)
      September-December 1960.
    - General, 1960 (Box 509, Folder 9)
      July-August 1960.
    - General, 1960 (Box 509, Folder 10)
      May-June 1960.
    - General, 1959-1960 (Box 509, Folder 11)
      December 1959-April 1960.
    - General, 1958-1959 (Box 510, Folder 1)
      March 1958-November 1959.
    - General, 1956-1958 (Box 510, Folder 2)
      September 1956-February 1958.
    - General, 1955-1956 (Box 510, Folder 3)
      December 1955-August 1956.
    - General, 1955 (Box 510, Folder 4)
      May-November 1955.
    - General, 1952-1955 (Box 510, Folder 5)
      November 1952-April 1955.
    - General, 1951-1952 (Box 510, Folder 6)
      1951-October 1952.
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 510, Folder 7)
      August 1949-50.
    - General, 1948-1949 (Box 510, Folder 8)
      August 1948-July 1949.
    - General, 1933-1946 (Box 510, Folder 9)
    - General, 1947-1948 (Box 510, Folder 10)
      1947-July 1948.
    - General, 1926 (Box 510, Folder 9-12)
    - General, 1924 (Box 510, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 337-1. United States Department of Labor
    - Bureau of Labor Statistics. Standing Committee of Union Research Directors, 1948-1950 (Box 511, Folder 1)
    - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1933-1936 (Box 511, Folder 2)
    - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1939-1943 (Box 511, Folder 3)
    - Bureau of Labor Statistics. Standing Committee of Union Research Directors, 1945-1947 (Box 511, Folder 4)
      November 1945-47.
    - Bureau of Labor Statistics. Standing Committee of Union Research Directors, 1940-1945 (Box 511, Folder 5)
      1940-October 1945.
    - Bureau of Labor Statistics. Standing Committee of Union Research Directors, 1941-1943 (Box 511, Folder 6)
    - Bureau of Labor Statistics. Standing Committee of Union Research Directors, 1943 (Box 511, Folder 7)
    - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1923-1926 (Box 511, Folder 8)
    - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1922 (Box 511, Folder 9)
    - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1929 (Box 511, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 337-2. United States Department of Labor
    - Women's Bureau, 1952-1954 (Box 511, Folder 11)
    - Women's Bureau, 1950-1951 (Box 511, Folder 12)
      June 1950-51.
    - Women's Bureau, 1948-1950 (Box 511, Folder 13)
      May 1948-May 1950.
    - Women's Bureau, 1947-1948 (Box 511, Folder 14)
      June 1947-April 1948.
    - Women's Bureau, 1936-1947 (Box 511, Folder 15)
      1936-May 1947.
    - Women's Bureau. Bulletins, 1947 (Box 511, Folder 16)
    - Women's Bureau, 1925-1926 (Box 511, Folder 17)
    - Women's Bureau, 1929-1930 (Box 511, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 337-3. United States Department of Labor
    - Immigration Laws, 1938-1955 (Box 511, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 337-4. United States Department of Labor
    - Research Agency, 1929 (Box 511, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 337-5. United States Department of Labor
    - Personnel, 1936-1954 (Box 511, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 337-6. United States Department of Labor
    - Labor Advisory Committee to the Agency for International Development, 1963-1964 (Box 512, Folder 1)
      February 1963-64.
    - Labor Advisory Committee to the Agency for International Development, 1960-1963 (Box 512, Folder 2)
      1960-January 1963.
    - Immigration over Canadian Boundary, 1940-1955 (Box 512, Folder 3)
    - Immigration over Canadian Boundary, 1932-1939 (Box 512, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 337-7. United States Department of Labor
    - Secretary of Labor, 1933-1954 (Box 512, Folder 5)
    - National Labor-Management Conference. General, 1945-1946 (Box 512, Folder 6)
    - National Labor-Management Conference. General, 1945 (Box 512, Folder 7)
      1945 November
    - National Labor-Management Conference. Official Documents, 1945 (Box 512, Folder 8-13)
    - National Labor-Management Conference. Official Documents, 1945 (Box 513, Folder 1-2)
  - Sub-Series 337-8. United States Department of Labor
    - United States Employment Service. Federal Advisory Council, 1934-1939 (Box 513, Folder 3)
    - United States Employment Service. Federal Advisory Council, 1940-1944 (Box 513, Folder 4)
    - United States Employment Service. Federal Advisory Council. Minutes and Proceedings, 1934-1939 (Box 513, Folder 5)
    - United States Employment Service. Federal Advisory Council, 1933 (Box 513, Folder 6)
    - United States Employment Service. Federal Advisory Council. Social Security Board, 1942 (Box 513, Folder 7)
    - United States Employment Service. Federal Advisory Council. Social Security Board. Proceedings, 1942 (Box 513, Folder 8)
      1942 January 9
    - United States Employment Service. Federal Advisory Council. Social Security Board. Proceedings, 1940 (Box 513, Folder 9-11)
      June 21-22, 1940.
    - United States Employment Service. Inventory of Job Seekers Registered at Public Employment Offices, 1940 (Box 513, Folder 12)
      1940 April
    - United States Employment Service. Specifications for Positions in State Employment Services Affiliated with United States Employment Service, 1936 (Box 513, Folder 13)
      1936 January 9
  - Sub-Series 337-9. United States Department of Labor
    - National Conference on Labor Legislation, 1953-1955 (Box 513, Folder 14)
    - National Conference on Labor Legislation, 1951-1952 (Box 513, Folder 15)
    - National Conference on Labor Legislation, 1948-1950 (Box 513, Folder 16)
      December 1948-50.
    - National Conference on Labor Legislation, 1948 (Box 514, Folder 1)
      January-November 1948.
    - Directory of Public Employment Offices Affiliated with Social Security Board, 1941 (Box 514, Folder 2)
      1941 January 1
    - National Conference on Labor Legislation, 1941-1947 (Box 514, Folder 3)
    - Sixth National Conference on Labor Legislation, 1939-1940 (Box 514, Folder 4)
    - Fifth National Conference on Labor Legislation, 1938 (Box 514, Folder 5)
    - National Conference on Labor Legislation, 1934-1937 (Box 514, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 337-10. United States Department of Labor
    - Division of Labor Standards, 1947-1956 (Box 514, Folder 7)
      September 1947-56.
    - Division of Labor Standards, 1946-1947 (Box 514, Folder 8)
      June 1946-August 1947.
    - Division of Labor Standards, 1936-1944 (Box 514, Folder 9)
    - Fifteenth National Conference on Labor Legislation. Proceedings, 1948 (Box 514, Folder 10)
      November 30, 1948-December 2, 1948.
    - National Labor-Management Conference, 1945 (Box 514, Folder 11)
      November 5-30, 1945.
    - Division of Labor Standards. Guide to Labor Legislation, 1944 (Box 514, Folder 12-13)
    - Division of Labor Standards. State and Federal Hours Limitations, 1942 (Box 514, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 337-11. United States Department of Labor
    - Children's Bureau, 1944-1959 (Box 514, Folder 15)
    - Children's Bureau, 1942-1943 (Box 514, Folder 16)
    - Children's Bureau. White House Conference on Children in a Democracy, 1940-1943 (Box 514, Folder 17)
      June 1940-January 1943.
    - Children's Bureau, 1940-1941 (Box 514, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 337-12. United States Department of Labor
    - Labor-Management Public Advisory Committee, 1953 (Box 514, Folder 19)
      February-August 1953.
    - Labor-Management Public Advisory Committee. Amendments Introduced in the Eighty-Third Congress to Amend or Repeal Labor-Management Relations Act of 1947 (Taft-Hartley Act), 1953 (Box 515, Folder 1)
      February-March 1953.
  - Sub-Series 337-13. United States Department of Labor
    - Legislative Summary, 1953-1956 (Box 515, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 337-14. United States Department of Labor
    - Welfare and Pension Plans Disclosure Act of 1958. Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 515, Folder 3)
      August 21, 1963-September 4, 1964.
    - Welfare and Pension Plans Disclosure Act of 1958. Reports, 1958-1963 (Box 515, Folder 4)
      1958-August 20, 1963.
  - Sub-Series 337-15. United States Department of Labor
    - Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act (Landrum-Griffin Act). Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 515, Folder 5)
      November 1959-March 1960.